A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
With the battle for Brew seemingly complete, each side moved on to the next step of their plan.
Some students, however, cannot forget their failure.
Meanwhile, I began investigating my dad's intentions for collecting Avon's dangerous works.
I wanted the truth.
But the information I obtained only deepened my suspicions of the Academy's recent activities.
I made it.
Death City, my new workplace.
Well, let's get started.
Scary.
君が望めば
どんな世界も
その目に映せるから
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby
怖い夢
だとしても
セレブル
君のために
星を砕ぎ
飾り付けた
Black paper
バッグ
知り合い
くれたなら
When you
ロスティー
を呼ぶ
Forever
With your
Soul
見上げれば
輝く
月のように
Forever
気
ford
burning
彼を
そ分の
彼の
wig
Do you prefer your full name, Joe Butataki,
or do you still go by JB?
Everything okay?
Yeah, yeah, everything's fine.
Let's talk about why you called me here.
Your summons seemed urgent.
Should I assume the project's already begun?
Aren't you getting a bit ahead of yourself?
I haven't even told you what you're doing here yet.
Yes, I'm sorry, but why else would you have called me
if not for that?
Of course that's why, but can't you let me say it?
You're kind of stealing my thunder here.
Besides, there are some new developments you should know about.
We lost our most recent battle with arachnophobia,
and Brew is now in their hands.
That makes your presence here all the more important.
It sounds like the Academy's at a serious disadvantage now.
Indeed we are, and I'm not sure there's much of anything I can do about it.
So what happens to the plan now that the enemy has Brew?
Well, fortunately, we've managed to acquire a number of Avon's other magic tools.
And that's where you come in.
What do you say?
Given the circumstances, can you help keep our plan on track?
The plan was my idea, and I'd hate to see it ruined.
I'll give it a try.
I knew I could count on you.
However, I have one condition before I start.
And that condition would be...
The coffee.
Coffee.
This is a disgrace. Instant coffee.
I won't work here until this shameful package has been stopped.
You must get rid of this disgusting powder and replace it with whole beans.
And they must come from Uncle Bob's.
Only the finest quality will do.
This point is non-negotiable.
I also require that you stock my preferred brand of coffee creamer.
Finally, the filters must be made of sturdy paper so no grounds will pollute the coffee.
Coffee beans?
Yes, coffee beans.
Ushera's Temptation. The big man's uncontrollable irritation?
You serious? First kid disappears, now Blackstar's taken off too?
What's gotten into everyone around here?
That's not all. Tsubaki's gone too.
I wonder what's going on?
Couldn't tell ya.
Something's been bothering Blackstar.
He hasn't been himself lately.
He seems so dispirited.
Why do I keep losing?
I'm supposed to be the one who surpassed God.
So why?
Why?
Why do you desire such great power?
Blackstar didn't show up to class. I wonder where he is.
Tsubaki.
Oh, hi, Nygus.
Do you have a sec?
What's a consultant from the tech division doing at the academy?
The news travels fast around here, doesn't it?
Only just got in and already the questions have started.
So who's that make you? The welcome wagon?
Death the Kid actually. I was named after my father.
I see. So you're Lord Death's little son, are you?
What brings you to the academy?
You've come a long way.
What part do you have to play in my dad's plans?
Construction.
The plumbing here at the academy is old. It's in pretty bad shape. That's why I'm here.
Not even a good lie.
You'll have to do better than that.
You wouldn't have come all this way for plumbing.
Well, of course, that isn't the only reason. The boiler needs some work done on it, too.
Now that's a job for the tech division, huh?
It might be if the academy had a boiler.
In the past few months, the academy's bent all its efforts on collecting magic tools.
And then out of nowhere, a technology expert just happens to show up.
So you'll excuse me if I think there's something more to this than our pipes.
Yeah.
If these magic tools are as rusty as my poker face, I'm gonna have a lot more work than I bargained for.
Come back. I'm not done talking.
Here's some free advice.
Huh?
Let it go. I'm here to do some work. That's all you need to know.
So tell me, how's Uncle Bob doing?
Uncle Bob?
The man who runs the coffee shop not far from here.
Uncle Bob's rumba coffee. It's so delicious it'll make you dance.
Come on, everybody, do the rumba. Shake your hips and do the Uncle Bob's coffee rumba with me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't know Uncle Bob?
That's a crying shame, kid.
Hey!
Here it is.
Lord Death's Vault. It's time to get started.
It's over, kid.
It isn't over yet. Not until I've beaten you!
Blackstar.
You don't understand the enchanted sword.
You won't ever be able to harness its full power.
You aren't strong enough.
What do you know? I'm Blackstar! I can do anything!
No. No, you can't.
It's all over. Just give up.
You have lost.
I've been looking all over for you.
I'm here.
It's the last place I checked, of course.
What are you doing here?
Thinking about how I'm gonna surpass God.
Why am I not surprised?
Should you be skipping class?
I skipped class to see where you were.
I didn't expect to end up on the roof, but here we are.
Yeah. Here we are.
I ran into Nygis.
She told me not to use the enchanted sword mode anymore.
What?
She said it's been putting too much strain on your body.
Yeah, right!
What a joke!
Nothing can make me give up on mastering the enchanted sword.
I understand.
How could you give up?
You haven't surpassed God yet.
No. Not yet.
What is it?
Oh, hey kid, you're back!
And where did you run off to?
Sorry, I was busy. I had some things to look into.
What kind of things?
What could be so important that you had to look into it without telling us where you were going?
I'll explain it later after class is over. It's a long story. For now, there's something else I need you to help me with.
What?
Where have you been, kid?
Is everything okay?
Of course. Everything's just fine.
I can't afford to let any of the other students know what I'm up to. It's too soon for that. For now, this investigation's a solo job.
It's Black Star.
You finally showed up. Do you know where you were going?
I'll explain it later after class is over. It's a long story. For now, there's something else I need you to help me with.
What?
Where have you been, kid?
Is everything okay?
Of course. Everything's just fine.
I can't afford to let any of the other students know what I'm up to. It's too soon for that. For now, this investigation's a solo job.
It's Black Star.
You finally showed up. Do you know what time it is?
I came for you, kid. Step outside for a second.
What's this about? Are you having some sort of a problem here?
I want to show you something.
What are you doing?
YAAA-HEA!
Not again!
Look what you did, you idiot! The DWMA building was perfectly symmetrical and now you've destroyed it!
How could you?!
Come on down here, kid.
Let's fight about it.
What?
So, how's Krona doing?
He's been acting strange lately. Something seems to be bothering him.
Why do you say that? Has he asked any questions recently that seem out of the ordinary for him?
Well, now that you mention it, he did ask about Stein's condition after the battle on Lost Island.
Oh? That is unexpected. Why would a child like Krona be concerned about Professor Stein?
I don't get it. He seemed really shaken up.
How unfortunate.
Poor Krona.
I don't think he'll be of use to me much longer.
What's going on? Why are you guys fighting?
I don't see what's so surprising. Blackstar gets into fights all the time.
Yeah, but still.
So, Blackstar.
Taking on Kid this time, are we?
The ref's here. We can get started now.
Hold on, both of you! What's the point of this stupid duel in the first place? This is ridiculous!
What, Tsubaki?
I'm sorry, but this is something Blackstar feels he has to do, so please don't interfere.
You brought this on yourself, Blackstar. You knew damn well how I'd react if the Academy's symmetry was destroyed.
Reaper combat art. Mortal sin stands.
There's no helping it. I have to beat you to a pulp very quickly, then immediately see to the necessary repairs.
Let's go.
You going to take your hands out of your pockets?
Are you trying to win this thing without using your hands?
Maybe I am.
Damn!
That's fast.
No time to block.
Here comes his soul wavelength.
It's all over.
What was that?
Blackstar.
Do you remember the first time we met?
We fought in this exact same place.
Since then, you've improved your fighting technique significantly.
You've got more style.
But I have to say,
you've gotten a bit weak.
Huh?
He's lost confidence in himself.
That's why his soul force attack didn't work.
His wavelength is paralyzed by doubt.
Is that even possible?
I've seen it happen before.
It doesn't take much to change his soul wavelength.
Doubting yourself will do it every time.
I've known Blackstar for a long time.
Since he was an infant.
He has great talent.
His soul is strong.
He's willing to work hard.
Against a single opponent or many, it doesn't matter.
He'll beat them all, one by one.
That's what he does.
That's who he is.
Someone who wins.
But lately, he's begun to lose fights, one after the other.
His battle with the samurai Mifune was the most damaging.
It was a total defeat.
If you think back, you'll see that was about the time when his attitude started to change.
He can't handle his recent losses.
He wasn't built to lose.
That's why he's been so angry?
It goes back even further, I think.
His difficulties with the enchanted sword have been a blow to his self-confidence.
I can't blame him.
Someone with a weaker soul would have given up a long time ago.
But that little idiot doesn't even know the meaning of giving up.
You're quiet.
Do you want to tell me what's on your mind?
What's on my mind?
Just that I'm surrounded by morons.
Why does he have to keep pushing himself so hard?
I'm sure he'll get the hang of it sooner or later if he'll just wait.
A long time ago, when I was alive, I was a handsome man.
We adults are often stuck in the past.
And children can only think about the future.
But Blackstar lives in the present.
He can't wait for the future.
He has to find his path now.
Find my path?
It's not about finding.
It's about winning.
Stop spouting your useless philosophies, stupid zombie.
Sid.
I see it.
Those eyes.
That wavelength.
Whitestar.
Is he following his father's path?
Blackstar, let's forget about the broken cone.
Just walk away.
I can't walk away now.
And I'll kill you before I let you give up either.
But you give up either.
You are so handsome, uncle.
Not looking for pain.
But you give up either.
isher.
What happened, Blackstar?
Who are you?
Your dream.
I thought you wanted to surpass God.
Um...
There's no need to apologize.
This isn't the last time it's going to happen.
It's who he is.
I know.
The important thing is what happens next.
Can he really keep living like this?
He's doing better now.
I think he'll be all right.
He's just got a few things left to learn.
That's all.
Hm.
Yeah.
I hope you're right.
What are you waiting for?
This was your idea.
Yeah, yeah.
I know, I know.
What's the big deal?
Just go in there and ask how he's doing or something.
Or do you not care about him at all?
How could you even say that?
He's our teammate.
Of course I care about him.
Then why are you still standing out here in the hall?
Get in there!
No, wait!
I haven't thought of something appropriate to say yet.
No, please, Sol!
33,456.
33,457.
33,458.
33,459.
33,460.
33,461.
33,462.
33,463.
33,464.
33,465.
33,466.
33,467.
33,468.
35,467.
34,468.
unfaced,
24,466.
3,469.
36,469.
33,469.
3,461.
33,467.
34,467.
24,469.
33,478.
33,469.
34,461.
64,479.
35,471.
36,471.
34,471.
35,471.
36,471.
How could he do this to me?
How am I supposed to dance the coffee rumba now?
Like this one
We'll be right back.
繰り返す毎日の腹波に伸ばれても まだ夢から覚める 俺たちはここにいる いつも聞こえてくる 仲間たちの声が 孤独を振り払うように 街の風の中 ただ会くしかないさ 信じた生き様を
蛇は9 Metal時のテーブルенияが  Their笑顔 なんだぜ かどうぞぼ 様ぼ っぼ せ
イヤ Kansas エンジンッ
but have fun on the next episode of soul eater crona's escape show me your smile please watch it
or i'll take your soul that's how it goes right